A Guide to the Western Fairfax County Survey Photograph Collection, 1976-1986 (bulk 1985-1986)
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Tax Map #: 40-3-A1, Victorian Farm House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-59, Frame #: 000
- Tax Map #: 40-3-A1, Victorian Farm House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-59, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 106-1-A1, Lundy House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-59, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 106-1-A1, Lundy House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-59, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 106-1-A1, Lundy House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-59, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 106-1-A1, Lundy House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-59, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 106-1-A1, Lundy House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-59, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 106-1-A1, Lundy House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-59, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 106-1-A1, Lundy House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-59, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 106-1-A1, Lundy House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-59, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 106-1-A1, Lundy House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-59, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 106-1-A1, Lundy House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-59, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 106-1-A1, Lundy House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-59, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 106-1-A1, Lundy House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-60, Frame #: 000
- Tax Map #: 106-1-A1, Lundy House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-60, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 106-1-A1, Lundy House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-60, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 106-1-A1, Lundy House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-60, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 106-1-A1, Lundy House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-60, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 106-1-A1, Lundy House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-60, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 106-1-A1, Lundy House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-60, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 106-1-A1, Lundy House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-60, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 106-1-A1, Lundy House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-60, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 106-1-A1, Lundy House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-60, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 106-1-A1, Lundy House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-60, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 106-1-A1, Lundy House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-60, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 106-1-A1, Lundy House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-60, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 106-1-A1, Lundy House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-60, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 30-2-A1, Sears House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-61, Frame #: 000
- Tax Map #: 30-2-A1, Sears House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-61, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 30-2-A1, Sears House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-61, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 30-2-A1, Sears House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-61, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 30-2-A1, Sears House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-61, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 30-2-A1, Sears House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-61, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 31-2-A1, Faulkner House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-61, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 40-3-A1, Victorian Farm House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-61, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 40-3-A1, Victorian Farm House, 1985 August; Roll #: 85-61, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 12-4-A1, Dr. Alfred Leigh House, 1985 September; Roll #: 85-62, Frame #: 000
- Tax Map #: 12-4-A1, Dr. Alfred Leigh House, 1985 September; Roll #: 85-62, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 12-4-A1, Dr. Alfred Leigh House, 1985 September; Roll #: 85-62, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 12-4-A1, Dr. Alfred Leigh House, 1985 September; Roll #: 85-62, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 12-4-A1, Dr. Alfred Leigh House, 1985 September; Roll #: 85-62, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 12-4-A1, Dr. Alfred Leigh House, 1985 September; Roll #: 85-62, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 12-4-A1, Dr. Alfred Leigh House, 1985 September; Roll #: 85-62, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 12-4-A1, Dr. Alfred Leigh House, 1985 September; Roll #: 85-62, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 12-4-A1, Dr. Alfred Leigh House, 1985 September; Roll #: 85-62, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 12-4-A1, Dr. Alfred Leigh House, 1985 September; Roll #: 85-62, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 12-4-A1, Dr. Alfred Leigh House, 1985 September; Roll #: 85-62, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 12-4-A1, Dr. Alfred Leigh House, 1985 September; Roll #: 85-62, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 12-4-A1, Dr. Alfred Leigh House, 1985 September; Roll #: 85-62, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 19-4-A1, Andrew Chapel School, 1985 September; Roll #: 85-62, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 19-4-A1, Andrew Chapel School, 1985 September; Roll #: 85-62, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 19-4-A1, Andrew Chapel School, 1985 September; Roll #: 85-62, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 19-4-A1, Andrew Chapel School, 1985 September; Roll #: 85-62, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 19-4-A1, Andrew Chapel School, 1985 September; Roll #: 85-62, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 19-4-A1, Andrew Chapel School, 1985 September; Roll #: 85-62, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 19-4-A1, Andrew Chapel School, 1985 September; Roll #: 85-62, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 19-4-A1, Andrew Chapel School, 1985 September; Roll #: 85-62, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 19-4-A1, Andrew Chapel School, 1985 September; Roll #: 85-62, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #: 34-2-A2, Groves House, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-63, Frame #: 000
- Tax Map #: 34-2-A2, Groves House, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-63, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 34-2-A2, Groves House, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-63, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 34-2-A2, Groves House, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-63, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A3, Site of Dairy Barns, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-63, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A3, Site of Dairy Barns, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-63, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A2, Dairy Barns, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-63, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A2, Dairy Barns, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-63, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A2, Dairy Barns, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-63, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A2, Dairy Barns, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-63, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A2, Dairy Barns, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-63, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A2, Dairy Barns, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-63, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A2, Dairy Barns, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-63, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A2, Dairy Barns, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-63, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A2, Dairy Barns, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-63, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A2, Dairy Barns, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-63, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A2, Dairy Barns, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-63, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 24-4-A2, Dairy Barns, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-63, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-63, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-63, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-63, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-63, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-63, Frame #: 022
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-63, Frame #: 023
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-63, Frame #: 024
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-63, Frame #: 025
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-63, Frame #: 026
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-63, Frame #: 027
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-63, Frame #: 028
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-63, Frame #: 029
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-63, Frame #: 030
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-63, Frame #: 031
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-63, Frame #: 032
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-63, Frame #: 033
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-63, Frame #: 034
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-63, Frame #: 035
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-63, Frame #: 036
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-63, Frame #: 037
- Tax Map #: 34-2-A4, Sully, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-64, Frame #: 000
- Tax Map #: 34-2-A4, Sully, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-64, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 34-2-A4, Sully, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-64, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 34-2-A4, Sully, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-64, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 34-2-A4, Sully, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-64, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 34-2-A4, Sully, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-64, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 34-2-A4, Sully, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-64, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 34-2-A4, Sully, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-64, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 34-2-A4, Sully, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-64, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 34-2-A4, Sully, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-64, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 34-2-A4, Sully, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-64, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 34-2-A4, Sully, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-64, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 34-2-A4, Sully, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-64, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 34-2-A4, Sully, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-64, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 34-2-A4, Sully, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-64, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 34-2-A4, Sully, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-64, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 34-2-A4, Sully, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-64, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 34-2-A2, Groves House, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-64, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 34-2-A2, Groves House, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-64, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 34-2-A2, Groves House, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-64, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 34-2-A2, Groves House, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-64, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 34-2-A2, Groves House, 1985 October; Roll #: 85-64, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A11, Ratcliff House, 1985 November; Roll #: 85-66, Frame #: 000
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A11, Ratcliff House, 1985 November; Roll #: 85-66, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A11, Ratcliff House, 1985 November; Roll #: 85-66, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A11, Ratcliff House, 1985 November; Roll #: 85-66, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A11, Ratcliff House, 1985 November; Roll #: 85-66, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A11, Ratcliff House, 1985 November; Roll #: 85-66, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A11, Ratcliff House, 1985 November; Roll #: 85-66, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A11, Ratcliff House, 1985 November; Roll #: 85-66, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A11, Ratcliff House, 1985 November; Roll #: 85-66, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A11, Ratcliff House, 1985 November; Roll #: 85-66, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A11, Ratcliff House, 1985 November; Roll #: 85-66, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A11, Ratcliff House, 1985 November; Roll #: 85-66, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A11, Ratcliff House, 1985 November; Roll #: 85-66, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A11, Ratcliff House, 1985 November; Roll #: 85-66, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 November; Roll #: 85-66, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 16-3-A4, McNair Farm, 1985 November; Roll #: 85-66, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A3, Dairy Farm, 1985 November; Roll #: 85-66, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A3, Dairy Farm, 1985 November; Roll #: 85-66, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A3, Dairy Farm, 1985 November; Roll #: 85-66, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A3, Dairy Farm, 1985 November; Roll #: 85-66, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A3, Dairy Farm, 1985 November; Roll #: 85-66, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A3, Dairy Farm, 1985 November; Roll #: 85-66, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A3, Dairy Farm, 1985 November; Roll #: 85-66, Frame #: 022
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A3, Dairy Farm, 1985 November; Roll #: 85-66, Frame #: 023
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A3, Dairy Farm, 1985 November; Roll #: 85-66, Frame #: 024
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A3, Dairy Farm, 1985 November; Roll #: 85-66, Frame #: 025
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A3, Dairy Farm, 1985 November; Roll #: 85-66, Frame #: 026
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A3, Dairy Farm, 1985 November; Roll #: 85-66, Frame #: 027
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A3, Dairy Farm, 1985 November; Roll #: 85-66, Frame #: 028
- Tax Map #: 45-1-A3, Dairy Farm, 1985 November; Roll #: 85-66, Frame #: 029
- Tax Map #: no site, Mike's Archaeology Photos, 1986 January 22; Roll #: 86-1, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: no site, Computer IBM PC, 1986 January 22; Roll #: 86-1, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: no site, Computer IBM PC, 1986 January 22; Roll #: 86-1, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 50-1-A1, Fountain of Faith (National Memorial Gardens), 1986 January 22; Roll #: 86-1, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 50-1-A1, Fountain of Faith (National Memorial Gardens), 1986 January 22; Roll #: 86-1, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 50-1-A1, Fountain of Faith (National Memorial Gardens), 1986 January 22; Roll #: 86-1, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 50-1-A1, Fountain of Faith (National Memorial Gardens), 1986 January 22; Roll #: 86-1, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 50-1-A1, Fountain of Faith (National Memorial Gardens), 1986 January 22; Roll #: 86-1, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #: 50-1-A1, Fountain of Faith (National Memorial Gardens), 1986 January 22; Roll #: 86-1, Frame #: 022
- Tax Map #: 50-1-A1, Fountain of Faith (National Memorial Gardens), 1986 January 22; Roll #: 86-1, Frame #: 023
- Tax Map #: 50-1-A1, Fountain of Faith (National Memorial Gardens), 1986 January 22; Roll #: 86-1, Frame #: 024
- Tax Map #: 50-1-A1, Fountain of Faith (National Memorial Gardens), 1986 January 22; Roll #: 86-1, Frame #: 025
- Tax Map #: 50-1-A1, Fountain of Faith (National Memorial Gardens), 1986 January 22; Roll #: 86-1, Frame #: 026
- Tax Map #: 50-1-A1, Fountain of Faith (National Memorial Gardens), 1986 January 22; Roll #: 86-1, Frame #: 027
- Tax Map #: 50-1-A1, Fountain of Faith (National Memorial Gardens), 1986 January 22; Roll #: 86-1, Frame #: 028
- Tax Map #: 50-1-A1, Fountain of Faith (National Memorial Gardens), 1986 January 22; Roll #: 86-1, Frame #: 029
- Tax Map #: 50-1-A1, Fountain of Faith (National Memorial Gardens), 1986 January 22; Roll #: 86-1, Frame #: 030
- Tax Map #: 50-1-A1, Fountain of Faith (National Memorial Gardens), 1986 January 22; Roll #: 86-1, Frame #: 031
- Tax Map #: 40-3-A1, Victorian Farm House, 1986 January 22; Roll #: 86-1, Frame #: 032
- Tax Map #: 40-3-A1, Victorian Farm House, 1986 January 22; Roll #: 86-1, Frame #: 033
- Tax Map #: 40-3-A1, Victorian Farm House, 1986 January 22; Roll #: 86-1, Frame #: 034
- Tax Map #: 40-3-A1, Victorian Farm House, 1986 January 22; Roll #: 86-1, Frame #: 035
- Tax Map #: 40-3-A1, Victorian Farm House, 1986 January 22; Roll #: 86-1, Frame #: 036
- Tax Map #: 40-3-A1, Victorian Farm House, 1986 January 22; Roll #: 86-1, Frame #: 037
- Tax Map #: no site, Merry Go Round (Inventory #202), 1976 April; Roll #: 86-2, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: no site, Merry Go Round (Inventory #202), 1976 April; Roll #: 86-2, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: no site, Adams…Sewell Cemetery (Inventory #208), 1976 April; Roll #: 86-2, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: no site, Adams…Sewell Cemetery (Inventory #208), 1976 April; Roll #: 86-2, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: no site, Adams…Sewell Cemetery (Inventory #208), 1976 April; Roll #: 86-2, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: no site, Frying Pan Farm Park (Inventory #211), 1976 April; Roll #: 86-2, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: no site, Frying Pan Farm Park (Inventory #211), 1976 April; Roll #: 86-2, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: no site, Frying Pan Farm Park (Inventory #211), 1976 April; Roll #: 86-2, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: no site, Frying Pan Farm Park (Inventory #211), 1976 April; Roll #: 86-2, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: no site, Turkey Run Farm (Inventory #210), 1976 April; Roll #: 86-2, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: no site, Turkey Run Farm (Inventory #210), 1976 April; Roll #: 86-2, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: no site, Turkey Run Farm (Inventory #210), 1976 April; Roll #: 86-2, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: no site, Centreville Earthworks, 1977 June; Roll #: 86-3, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: no site, Centreville Earthworks, 1977 June; Roll #: 86-3, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: no site, Centreville Earthworks, 1977 June; Roll #: 86-3, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: no site, Stoneybrook (Inventory #195), 1977 June; Roll #: 86-3, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: no site, Stoneybrook (Inventory #195), 1977 June; Roll #: 86-3, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: no site, Stoneybrook (Inventory #195), 1977 June; Roll #: 86-3, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: no site, Stoneybrook (Inventory #195), 1977 June; Roll #: 86-3, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: no site, Stoneybrook (Inventory #195) [unidentified mid-century house], 1977 June; Roll #: 86-3, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: no site, Indian Springs Farm (Inventory #196), 1977 June; Roll #: 86-3, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: no site, Indian Springs Farm (Inventory #196), 1977 June; Roll #: 86-3, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: no site, Indian Springs Farm (Inventory #196), 1977 June; Roll #: 86-3, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: no site, Newington Railroad Station Freight Office, 1977 June; Roll #: 86-3, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: no site, Manassas Battlefield, 1977 June; Roll #: 86-3, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: no site, Manassas Battlefield, 1977 June; Roll #: 86-3, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: no site, Herndon Railroad Station (Inventory #186), 1977 June; Roll #: 86-3, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: no site, Herndon Railroad Station (Inventory #186), 1977 June; Roll #: 86-3, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: no site, Herndon Railroad Station (Inventory #186), 1977 June; Roll #: 86-3, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #: no site, Hatmark School (Inventory #223), 1980 June; Roll #: 86-4, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: no site, Hatmark School (Inventory #223), 1980 June; Roll #: 86-4, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: no site, Holmes Run Acres (Inventory #222), 1980 June; Roll #: 86-4, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: no site, Holmes Run Acres (Inventory #222), 1980 June; Roll #: 86-4, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: no site, Holmes Run Acres (Inventory #222), 1980 June; Roll #: 86-4, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: no site, Holmes Run Acres (Inventory #222), 1980 June; Roll #: 86-4, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: no site, Holmes Run Acres (Inventory #222), 1980 June; Roll #: 86-4, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: no site, Holmes Run Acres (Inventory #222), 1980 June; Roll #: 86-4, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: no site, Holmes Run Acres (Inventory #222), 1980 June; Roll #: 86-4, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: no site, Tudor Hall (Inventory #214), 1980 June; Roll #: 86-4, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: no site, Tudor Hall (Inventory #214), 1980 June; Roll #: 86-4, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: no site, Tudor Hall (Inventory #214), 1980 June; Roll #: 86-4, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: no site, Tudor Hall (Inventory #214), 1980 June; Roll #: 86-4, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: no site, Civil War drawings of Ft. Ramsey, 1980 June; Roll #: 86-4, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: no site, Civil War drawings of Ft. Ramsey, 1980 June; Roll #: 86-4, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: no site, Civil War drawings of Ft. Ramsey, 1980 June; Roll #: 86-4, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: no site, Civil War drawings of Ft. Ramsey, 1980 June; Roll #: 86-4, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: no site, Civil War drawings of Ft. Ramsey, 1980 June; Roll #: 86-4, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: no site, Civil War drawings of Ft. Ramsey, 1980 June; Roll #: 86-4, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: no site, Civil War drawings of Ft. Ramsey, 1980 June; Roll #: 86-4, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 59--A1, Holmes Run Acres, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-5, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 59--A1, Holmes Run Acres, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-5, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 59--A1, Holmes Run Acres, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-5, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 59--A1, Holmes Run Acres, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-5, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 59--A1, Holmes Run Acres, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-5, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 59--A1, Holmes Run Acres, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-5, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 59--A1, Holmes Run Acres, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-5, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 59--A1, Holmes Run Acres, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-5, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 59--A1, Holmes Run Acres, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-5, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 59--A1, Holmes Run Acres, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-5, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 48-3-A1, House - BE&K Communications, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-5, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 48-3-A1, House - BE&K Communications, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-5, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 48-3-A1, House - BE&K Communications, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-5, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 48-3-A1, House - BE&K Communications, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-5, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 48-3-A1, House - BE&K Communications, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-5, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 48-3-A1, House - BE&K Communications, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-5, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 48-3-A1, House - BE&K Communications, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-5, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 48-1-A1, Hunter House, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-5, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 48-1-A1, Hunter House, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-5, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 48-1-A1, Hunter House, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-5, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 48-1-A1, Hunter House, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-5, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #: 48-1-A1, Hunter House, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-5, Frame #: 022
- Tax Map #: 48-1-A1, Hunter House, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-5, Frame #: 023
- Tax Map #: 48-1-A1, Hunter House, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-5, Frame #: 024
- Tax Map #: no site, Huntley (Inventory #135), 1986 February; Roll #: 86-7, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: no site, Huntley (Inventory #135), 1986 February; Roll #: 86-7, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: no site, Huntley (Inventory #135), 1986 February; Roll #: 86-7, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: no site, Huntley (Inventory #135), 1986 February; Roll #: 86-7, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: no site, Huntley (Inventory #135), 1986 February; Roll #: 86-7, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: no site, Huntley (Inventory #135), 1986 February; Roll #: 86-7, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: no site, Huntley (Inventory #135), 1986 February; Roll #: 86-7, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: no site, Huntley (Inventory #135), 1986 February; Roll #: 86-7, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: no site, Huntley (Inventory #135), 1986 February; Roll #: 86-7, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: no site, Huntley (Inventory #135), 1986 February; Roll #: 86-7, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: no site, Huntley (Inventory #135), 1986 February; Roll #: 86-7, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: no site, Huntley (Inventory #135), 1986 February; Roll #: 86-7, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: no site, Huntley (Inventory #135), 1986 February; Roll #: 86-7, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: no site, Huntley (Inventory #135), 1986 February; Roll #: 86-7, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: no site, Huntley (Inventory #135), 1986 February; Roll #: 86-7, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: no site, Huntley (Inventory #135), 1986 February; Roll #: 86-7, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: no site, Huntley (Inventory #135), 1986 February; Roll #: 86-7, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: no site, Huntley (Inventory #135), 1986 February; Roll #: 86-7, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: no site, Huntley (Inventory #135), 1986 February; Roll #: 86-7, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: no site, Huntley (Inventory #135), 1986 February; Roll #: 86-7, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: no site, Huntley (Inventory #135), 1986 February; Roll #: 86-7, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #: no site, Huntley (Inventory #135), 1986 February; Roll #: 86-7, Frame #: 022
- Tax Map #: 40-3-A1, Victorian Farm House, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-8, Frame #: 000
- Tax Map #: 40-3-A1, Victorian Farm House, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-8, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 40-3-A1, Victorian Farm House, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-8, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 40-3-A1, Victorian Farm House, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-8, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 40-3-A1, Victorian Farm House, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-8, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 40-3-A1, Victorian Farm House, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-8, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: no site, Dunn Loring, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-8, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: no site, Dunn Loring, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-8, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: no site, Dunn Loring, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-8, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: no site, Dunn Loring, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-8, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: no site, Dunn Loring, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-8, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: no site, Dunn Loring, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-8, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: no site, Dunn Loring, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-8, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: no site, Dunn Loring, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-8, Frame #: 013